const data =[
    {
        question:'1. One of Vietnamese traditions is a belief in _______ families and in preserving their cultures.',
        options: ['A. wealthy','B. secure','C. safe','D. close-knit'],
        correct_option:'D. close-knit',
        note:''

    },
    {
        question:'2. - “Don’t forget to come tomorrow.”   - “______”    ',
        options: ["A. I don’t",'B. I won’t','C. I can’t ','D. close-knit'],
        correct_option:'B. I won’t',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:'3. I last heard this song ten years ago.',
        options: ["A. It is ten years since I last heard this song.",'B. It is ten years when I have heard this song.','C. It has been ten years when I have heard this song','D. It was ten years since I have heard this song'],
        correct_option:'A. It is ten years since I last heard this song.',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:'4. We are a very close-nit family and very _____of one another.',
        options: ['A. supporting ','B. supportive','C. support','D. supporter'],
        correct_option:'B. supportive',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:'5. Members of our family have very close relationships ______each other.',
        options: ['A. with','B.  of','C. among','D. at'],
        correct_option:'D. at',
        note:'Night shift : ca đêm'
    },
    {
        question:'6. His eel soup is ______best soup I have ever eaten.',
        options: ['A. the','B. a','C. an','D. no article'],
        correct_option:'A. the',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:'7. Dad is always willing to ______a hand with cleaning the house.',
        options: ['A. take	','B. give','C. make','D. do'],
        correct_option:'B. give',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:'She got up late and RUSHED to the bus stop. (RUSHED - OPPOSITE)',
        options: ['A. came into ','B. went leisurely','C. went quickly','D. dropped by'],
        correct_option:'B. went leisurely',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:"Whenever problems COME UP, we discuss them frankly and find solutions quickly.(COME UP - CLOSEST)",
        options: ['A. happen','B. encounter','C. arrive','D. clean'],
        correct_option:'A. happen',
        note:''
    },
    {
        question:"10. The twins like two ____in the same pot, I can’t tell them apart though I meet them everyday at class.",
        options: ['A. peas','B. beans','C. apples   ','D. peanuts'],
        correct_option:'A. peas',
        note:''
    },
]
export default data;
